* Features

* How It Works

* How To's

Privacy Policy
==============

We respect your privacy and therefore we strive to protect it!

Privacy Policy Duplicate Files Fixer
------------------------------------

duplicatefilesfixer.com is strongly committed to protect your privacy and provide a safe online experience for all of our users and registered customers while offering the highest quality products and services to them. We may gather certain types of information about and from you to fulfill your request and serve your needs better, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions covering the collection and use of this information. This privacy statement discloses what information we may gather, how we may use it and how to correct or change it.  
Please read the “Privacy Policy” completely, as well as our ‘Terms and Conditions' for use of information we may gather. Should you have any questions in this regard, feel free to contact us.

What Information we may collect about you?
------------------------------------------

You can visit our website, read products description and other materials, and check on offerings without giving us any personally identifiable information. Since we provide our customers and newsletter subscribers with the most efficient and enhanced personalized service; we may request information about you under occasional circumstances. For your convenience and to serve you better, a customer account includes all the collected personal information we may have; however, you can update or correct your contact information or change your preferences about receiving newsletter and other information from us.

We collect personally identifiable information; such as name, mailing address and e-mail address when you register to one of our products or place an order (see the section below for more information on placing order). Website visitors may register to receive our newsletter by submitting their name and e- mail address.

**Data Protection for Sensitive Information:**

We take the security of your personally identifiable information and other sensitive data seriously. Our application employs industry-standard encryption techniques, including SSL/TLS for data in transit and AES-256 for data at rest, ensuring your data is always safeguarded. Additionally, access to sensitive information is limited to authorized personnel trained in securely handling user data. We adhere to strict protocols to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure, or alteration of your data, including using multi-factor authentication (MFA) and regular security audits.

Additional Information
----------------------

Our Product may have the functionality to allow you to access your files stored in online storage spaces such as Google Drive, Dropbox and Amazon S3 Servers, or other services as and when added. This functionality allows you to check for duplicate files stored online on these storage spaces. You will have to authorize the Product to access your files stored at such online servers. We do not store your credentials for any of these servers or storage spaces at any time. These storage services providers may provide details of your files, their size, and/or their MD5 or other Hash identifiers. Access to this information is limited to the PC on which the application is being used on, and is never shared with, or stored on any of our servers.  
There may be additional Privacy Policy of these service providers that you may have already accepted, or will need to accept, to use the services provided by the Online Service Providers with the Product. You are required to check the websites of the service providers for their privacy policy and requirements.  
The use of this Product to search and identify duplicate files on your PC is uninterrupted even without accessing the Online Storage Services in case you do not have any account with them or do not wish to connect your online accounts with the Product.

We do not collect or store any personally identifiable information (PII) from your Google account or other online services on our servers. The application temporarily accesses files solely to identify duplicate files within your cloud storage. Once the duplicate scan is completed or the session expires due to inactivity, all access tokens and temporary credentials are automatically deleted from your system. In accordance with Google’s data retention policies, permissions granted to the application can be revoked at any time through your Google account settings. No information is retained post-usage, and users can manually delete cached data by navigating to Help & Clear Cache within the app. For additional assistance, users may contact our support team.

Placing order
-------------

If you wish to place an order for our products, you can generally enter the requisite details. In addition to the customary information that may be required to fill your order (full name, address, phone number, ship-to name and address etc.), collection of additional information such as your credit card number and credit card expiration date, is dependent on option of payment as we offer online and offline subscribers additional options such as check, money order and credit card order by fax or phone.

What we may do with the information we collect?
-----------------------------------------------

We use information you provide to fulfill your request and improve our products and services. We may use personal information to display or send personalized content to our website visitors as well as to send newsletter, product features, promotional material, special offers and other updates to our customers and newsletter subscribers. A subscriber may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our products and services, resolve customers' issues like respond to any problems that may arise such as product delivery failures, difficulties in navigating our sites or accessing certain features as well as to gauge user trends to determine what products are most popular with users.  
We allow users of our website to email us their queries. We do not retain any email address (unless you are a member who already has voluntarily provided your email address) of either the sender or recipient of such e-mail or links after they are sent.

How do we share Personal Information?
-------------------------------------

We may share your personal information with the parties described below:

Credit Card Companies:
----------------------

Credit card numbers are only shared with our partners with whom you place an online order. They process the billing of such products on our behalf. Rest assured that we and our payment gateways follow careful procedures to safeguard credit card data in connection with your transactions.

Payment Gateways:
-----------------

In no event will duplicatefilesfixer.com be liable for any damages, including without limitation, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, whether under a contract, tort or any other theory of liability, arising in connection with any party's use of the website or in connection with any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, line system failure, loss of data, or loss of use related to this website or any website operated by any third party or any contents of this website or any other website, even if duplicatefilesfixer.com is aware of the possibility of such damages.

Important Note:
---------------

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation.

Cookies Policy
--------------

We and our partners gather information via "cookies" enabled in the browser and use other alike tracking technologies to study trends, track users' activity on the website, and collect statistical data about website visitors, manage the website. As we know cookies is a small text file stored by the web browser when enabled via settings. Session cookies and persistent cookies may be used to know you have logged in, when and how our website and services are used, and to check usage and traffic on the website.

When you close the browser, or log out from the account, session cookies automatically get removed. At any time, you can stop site from saving cookies but doing same may not allow you to access our software and services completely.

We use own and third-party cookies to show personalized content and ads on Systweak’s properties and other sites, to provide social media features, to create an anonymous profile based on browsing behavior (visited pages, frequency, time) and to analyze how our services are used. By clicking on the site, you accept their use.

Links
-----

duplicatefilesfixer.com may offer links to or from websites it controls to other sites. We offer links to some renowned websites that review and rate our products and market them so that you can be conversant on authenticity of products performance. These links may also be to websites that duplicatefilesfixer.com promotes, whether internal or external. Duplicatefilesfixer.com may receive an incentive to promote these links or through your purchase or actions on the websites at these links.

Changes to Privacy Policy
-------------------------

We will occasionally update “Privacy Policy” as necessary to protect you to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the policy when you visit our site to be sure you are aware of and understand the prevailing policy. If we make material changes to this policy we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make material changes in how we may handle any of your previously collected personal information that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so, and we will e-mail registered customers and newsletter subscribers information on material changes to this policy.

* 
* 
* 
* 

Site Links
----------

Features
--------

Get Duplicate Files Fixer
-------------------------

Follow Us
---------

Copyright © Systweak Software All rights reserved.

This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. [View Privacy Policy](https://www.duplicatefilesfixer.com/privacy-policy/#cookies)

OK
